Hello friends, welcome back to our channel. So
today in this video we will talk
about ICICI Lord General Insurance. We have
covered ICICI Lord before and
after that you will see what kind of
traction was seen. If you have
n't seen that video of mine, you can definitely go and watch it.
You will find the video on this channel.
We have talked about
many stocks before. In the last
video itself, I told you about Texam Rail
and Texam Rail also has very
good chart patterns. If you have
n't seen that video, please go and watch it
because there has been a very good
breakout there and now you can
see very good traction in it. So, to keep
seeing such ideas in the future,
please subscribe to my channel and don't
forget to press the bell icon. If you like the videos, then do
like and
share with your friends. Today let's quickly talk
about ICICI Lombard. There was
a level in ICICI Lord which was causing
trouble for it, around 730.  If
you look at this level here, it has faced resistance at 730
many times and now
it has taken
out this significant level around 1730 and very
good traction can be seen now, so
what should you do if you have a position,
if you have a position then you can definitely stay there
and if you are thinking of opening a position now
then you
can see a rally of up to 50 which will
take it almost to 22000, so
you can definitely wait for up to ₹
1789 is currently running, so if you
want to open a new position then what should you do,
for opening a new position the closer you get to 1730
the better it will be for you and 1724 will
work as a stop loss which is
also its 20 dema, so this support should be taken at 20 dema
and after that it
should resume an upward trajectory because the
chart patterns are very good
and this one which is in front of you is  It has shown a kind of
V-shaped recovery. From here,
that V-shaped recovery looks very good.
And if you also look at the RSI, then the RSI is
also very good at 67. The only
thing in it is that now it is
going towards a little consolidation phase. If you
will see this, the volume has also dropped right now.
What does this drop in volume mean?
Either it should consolidate here or it should immediately
spend some time at
this level around 1730,
it can spend time around 1730, 1790. So, it has some very
good chart patterns. If
you have a position, then you can stay there and
with a strict stop loss because as I am
telling you in every video that the
market is moving at the top and the time has come to be a little cautious.
And for this reason, whatever
position you take, take it with a little break stop loss, otherwise it can happen that
you can get trapped in
it. So, at the levels at which
all the stocks are moving right now, but
ICICI Lombard is in a good sector and it is
in the insurance sector.  And the management of the company is
good, this stock comes from the house of IIC,
so all those things
look fundamentally strong for it as well, so this is the
daily chart, keep in
mind as a disclaimer in this, I do not have any position, but it is
possible that I may take a position
in the future, so whatever decision you take, take it
only after discussing with your financial advisor, otherwise
this is the daily
chart, let's look at the weekly chart once,
how is its place on the weekly chart,
you will see this on the weekly chart also, there was
a level which it has broken, it was quite
significant, that was around 1680,
when did it touch 1680, it touched 1680 almost
in September 202,
this level was around 1670 7580,
see, it spent a lot of time here, it
consolidated a bit and came down as well, but
now it has shown very good
traction and in week three,
it has shown very good traction since the last three weeks, so
if June 10th
If we look at the week of June, there was a
return of 45, after that it was at 1 and now
%, so if you look at the three-week rally in this, the
three-week rally has been very good
and the resistance which was acting at
16,7580, it has now
removed it significantly and one more thing is that
now it has already removed the last hurdle which was
around 1750
and now it has
also removed the levels of 1735, 1730, 1750 and now a
very good rally can be seen in this, so the
first stop is of 2000 but if you look at the
rounding bottom which it has created on this weekly chart, it is a
huge rounding
bottom, if you look at the target of this rounding bottom, then
you may get to
see a target of around 2250,
so the first stop will be
2000 and the second 22250, so this
Be very careful about these two levels and keep
trailing your stop losses because if
it crosses the 2000 level, then
trail your stop loss to 2000
and you can wait for 2250. So
this is what happens on the weekly chart.
If you have the
RAI of RSIC on the weekly chart, then that is also a clear
indication that it is showing you a good
momentum and you can see
that whatever green candle is forming in it,
in the volume bar below, that green candle is
becoming bigger and the red candle is becoming smaller. So this is
also a clear indication that when it is going up, it is
going with the volume. But when it has come down, then the
volume is drying up a bit. So
that is another good indicator. It can happen
in ICICI Lombard that it may take
some time. ICICI Lombard, as
I told you, so do
not write in the comments that it will work tomorrow
or it will work on Monday, it may not work
even if it does not work on Monday, it will not work for a week.  It can also run but it looks like a
very good bet in the long term. The
target of 2250 is clearly visible
on the charts but with a strict stop
loss, I tell you this again and again, let us take a
look at the monthly chart,
how is its place on the monthly chart, so the
monthly chart is also placed in front of you, here also you will
clearly see that it is a very good picture,
it has started moving upwards by making a perfect rounding bottom
and now in this month it
showed a rally of 13, which
in the last month it showed a rally of almost 7.5, so from the
rally of 7.5 and
now the rally it showed at 13 131 is
very good, what is the good thing about it, the
support it took at 1480 was
near its 20 month exponential moving average which was 1467, 20
month exponential moving average and the
low it showed in this month was 1480, so
it  It started moving upwards taking support at the right place,
that is also a good thing. Now let
me also look at the Fona levels in this.
From the Fona point of view, which
targets emerge, so keep this in
mind on the monthly chart in front of you.
I am putting Fona levels.
If you look at the monthly T levels,
1675 was the first target, but now if you look at the next stop, the next stop is
coming at 2060.
After 2060, 2684. So keep these two levels in
mind. I had told you about 2000.
From the Fona point of view, the 2060
level is emerging and if you look at the second stop, the
2684 level is emerging, so a
rally up to ₹2000000 can also be seen. You
can definitely stay in ICICI Lombard. Although there
is no recommendation, still the chart
patterns look very good and
I am telling you all this from the chart point of view only.
Even on the monthly chart, if you see the
chart pattern of RSIC on the time frame, it looks very good. If you have a position
of ICICI Lombard, then stay there. If you
want to create a new position, then you can definitely do so. The
closer you get to 1730, the better it is.
And with a strict stop loss of 1730. So
this is my view on ICICI Lombard.
If you have a position, then
definitely tell me in the comments and at which
level did you enter and what is your long
term target. You are definitely watching the videos
but are not liking or
sharing the videos. That would be my one
request that if you are liking the videos and
finding the content good, then do
like the videos and
share them with your friends. And if you
are new to my channel and have
not yet subscribed to my channel, then quickly
subscribe to the channel. Do not forget to press the bell icon. That is all for
today's video. We will
see you in the next video.
Thank you so much for watching this video.